What have we been in the case? The answer is next year. One church, takes a break and carries it on you too Mister Lloyd Thank You for like us to gather here today his place all of our conversations so as be able
We've been shooting for the amount of $14,163.50 cents
Yes board so we know
that recently had a meeting with them
and they kind give us an update on everything
I have going onto
And this claim is approved
It'll leave it some remaining balance
Of 565 thousand
480 dollars in 79 cents
For The Year
So if you remember
Where were started?
Budget 740
More to approve
The step
Double
Hi
Jim
Side
Bar
Parker
Five
Eight
Ward-Laysburg
Archers Agreement to Fake
Of Grant Lake
For Q24-78
Peterville at Day Cab
567 truck
We've related
Sonding of Payment Authority
To Zemander
Is Designee
we are buying this
Truck on a source well number
And
went out
Five Wending Institutions
Interest rates ranged from
five
Fifteen down
The 467
This item requires
A payment plan
DePurchase
The purchase amount is
171,000
And
Security Bank
Didn't bid
Our Vest
Came in at 515
Welts State
At 498
First National
Four
Eight
One
and Bank of Grant Lake
came
InAt 467
We recommend setting up a
Lease contract
With bank
Of grant lake
To make this
Purchases
When each are approved
Which was Truck
Fourth
This
Is For the Electric
DePartignet
And this is a
Tired Question
But This Is Budget
Was the Truck budget
Just Had To Ask
The Commission Way Approved
Hi
John
All right
No, I know that you can't
Be near what's in prison
Supposed to Disagenda
Ten Staff Report
And trustee Canadian Altsbook
For adjournment
Second
Aye
Stop
John
High
Good
Alright